Hello Hello friends welcome to share market
how much income a person can get here check
stock option kaise banaye from edit only then date of
which Sivalingam
Reddy ICICI Lombard
NMB in one general meeting will be held in front of the company
if we
can see here how much income from the statement of a company like
Sanju a year ago like stock option brand
50 and if we were from last year then we got a
call from tubewell company that the company is
generating its income, we can see it is
amazing so today
or disruption in employment is very much
use of such exercise definition of HP
friends and if we see the expenses of the company here then
for eligible employees which is like this out of this
see the pimples loudly which is quite good here so
when this meeting is going on subscribe to one and a half listing
and subscribe to the channel
see the net profit of the company here
full time director will also be of the company which is the
company which has generated a little income at this time that is a  The
number that the bot employee can stock
which will be the profit after tax is the
second thing that will have to be done,
if we talk about it
and in the video we will
see the profit as per 300 crores,
focus on its result now I have seen here
but
according to the option scheme 2005 in quarter by quarter, it has been 4.57
lakh front, the
result of this company's income has been good but friends,
whereas in December one cotton can be 300 crores,
which friends we can subscribe these three,
like stock option of 6 crores one million, the company has
cost so much that the company has got the profit in
months and these earrings, you can see the result of both, see
Mriga,
for the contra like, in the profit, you can see a lot of
approval, you can see the
smooth looking number of such a company is in lakhs and in
which the
company has made a lot of profit in the voucher and if the
statement has come, you can see and there has been a
lot of impact, so friends,
start the result in this  Friends, if you feel that the income
like dividend is quite solid
which can be taken in the market meeting,
friends, approximately this is the price for grand
friends and if we
can invest a little in it like in its near cases, we have done
501, the
price will be 3863 on equity shares,
talk about the total income, see that the total income, as
you are getting to see a lot of don in one and a half and the company by commenting,
show
4636 crores, the total income of the company from Kiradu,
its profit after that, now this is
very great for market thinking, so friends
subscribe and share and if the company is doing this,
now we love the video,
subscribe and we can see that the
market
Meghnad company is getting to
see this from a very negative level and if you
liked the video then like it, if anyone wants to see
its December 21
diet, then to see the profit of ICICI Lombard Stocks in it, if
it is negative
then ask in the comment box, you get to
see the darling [ __ ] of 600 crores  You
can get to see the chances of getting it, so
along with that, and
in the next video we are going to see land by
and you can see the company's thing immediately,
friends, if we talk about segment subscription here, then the
segment of the company is
quarter per quantum, in a very easy way from
which we can
oppose and if we look at this front of the
company, which
can be seen, net premium, don't have any, we
can get it, it is very much
seen, Dixit is almost
their idol, then the income from the
husband, which is Rs. 10000 last year, like
in its general meeting,
sorry friends,
investors learning, from all these things, you
can see in the Rauniyar, that income of Rs. 1100 crore
of the company is generated, you can see it,
final friends, you will get to know that friends,
you can pause the video and
see the result that if we Sharif Hardik can
[Music]